Guide to the General Frederick Steele Papers, 1845-1965 (inclusive), 1862-1868 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series II. Katherine B. Steele Papers
  - MRS. CATHERINE STEELE'S BIOGRAPHICAL WORK ON GEN: STEELE.
    - Typescript A: Introduction - Preface. (Box 17, Folder 10.)
      Outlines, Greene Oaks, Steele family in Calif., the Civil War chest.
    - Typescript A: Introduction - Chapter I, What Boy Could Forget. (Box 17, Folder 11.)
      FS's youth and years at Westpoint.
    - Typescript A: Introduction - Chapter II, The Soldier. (Box 17, Folder 12.)
      Buffalo Barracks, Anti-Rent Riot, death of Osman Steele, Fort Mackinac.
    - Typescript A: Introduction - Chapter III, The Mexican War. (Box 17, Folder 13.)
      Mexican War and Fort Hamilton.
    - Typescript A: Introduction - Chapter IV, California. (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Carlisle Barracks, Dreams of the Visionary, Steele brothers and ranching in California.
    - Typescript A: Introduction - Chapter V, Prelude to the Civil War. (Box 17, Folder 15)
      The Indian Frontier, death of FS's mother, A Visit to J. B. Steele in Kingston, N.Y., 1860; The War Democrat (JBS).
    - Typescript A: Part I, Folder II, Missouri-Arkansas 1861-62. (Box 17, Folder 16)
      Nathaniel Lyon, Dug Springs, Wilson's Creek, St. Louis, Sedalia, Jennison, Ark. 1862; Court of Inquiry.
    - Typescript A: Pt. I, Folder III, The Little Colored Girl. (Box 17, Folder 17)
      Emancipation Outline; Dr. Dicken, Mr. Craig and Bostevick. This folder also contains variant versions since this chapter or topic only appears in this version of the typescripts.
    - Typescript A: Pt. I, Folder IV, Vicksburg. (Box 17, Folder 18)
      Chicasaw Bluffs, Arkansas Post, Young's Point, Jackson, Vicksburg.
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder I, The Arkansas Campaign. (Box 17, Folder 19)
      Davidson, operations against and capture of Little Rock.
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder II, The Department of Arkansas. (Box 17, Folder 20)
      Administrative policy, creation of Department, appointment of FS as commander, Sickles, quarrel with Davidson.
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder III, The General Commanding. (Box 17, Folder 21)
      Arkansas, military districts, etc.; Post of Little Rock, etc; reconstruction policy; National Democrat; Freedmen's Bureau; case of Sandy Redmond; Treasury regulations and oath of allegiance; slavery; cotton-fraud, etc.; requests for compensation; recommendations; rebel activities; Autumn 1863; Caldwell expedition; guerrillas and Home Guards; Christmas; charity and Sanitary Fairs; young spy; West Point battle monument; kindness and favors; fraudulent oaths.
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder IV, The Conciliatory Policy. (Box 17, Folder 22)
      Arkansas state elections and new state government; radicals; politics.
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder V, The Red River Expedition. (Box 17, Folder 23)
      Banks; military activity; Camden; Jenkins' Ferry
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder VI, The Best You Can Do. (Box 17, Folder 24)
      Prisoners of war; department duties and social activities; Red River Expedition; news from Washington; death of Manter; Davidson's charges-bribery, etc.; crade; Arkansas politicians; McClellan for President; Congress refuses to seat Arkansas delegates; taxes; military commissions and trials; attacks on FS and his policy; change of Dept. commanders.
    - Typescript A: Pt. II, Folder VII, Holding the Line. (Box 17, Folder 25)
      Military activities; Price in Missouri; rumors and intelligence; Davidson's charges.
    - Typescript A: Pt. III, Folder I, Blakely. (Box 17, Folder 26)
      Louisiana 1865; Spanish Fort; Blakely. Two slightly different versions.
    - Typescript A: Pt. III, Folder II, Last Days of the War. (Box 17, Folder 27)
      Mobile; death of Lincoln; Sherman's armistice; Selmo; Montgomery; Taylor's surrender.
    - Typescript A: Pt. III, Folder III, Rio Grande. (Box 17, Folder 28)
      Texas; cotton; Mejia and Cortina; Matamoros and Brownsville; Isaac Suratt; removal of FS.
    - Typescript A: Pt. III, Folder IV, The Department of the Columbia (Box 17, Folder 29)
      San Francisco; Oregon; Washington Territory; Idaho; Fort Boise; Gen. Crook; Indians.
    - Typescript A: Pt. III, Folder V, Lone Mountain. (Box 17, Folder 30)
      FS relieved from duty; leave in San Francisco; death.
    - Typescript B: Introduction, Ch. I, Ano Nuevo. (Box 17, Folder 31)
      [Ano Nuevo, La Punta del Ano Nuevo, Rancho]; The Steale Brothers; Green Oaks; [The Attic, A Civil War Chest, Memories, Ole Abe, the Bitterness of Reconstruction]; Conciliatory Policy; How Ephemeral Fame; Pensively Waiting.
    - Typescript B: Introduction, Ch. II, Genealogy. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Typescript B: Introduction, Ch. III, Youth. (Box 17, Folder 33)
      West Point; appearance of FS; death of Osman Steele; Fort Mackinac.
    - Typescript B: Introduction, Ch. IV, First Battles. (Box 17, Folder 34)
      Mexican War; California; Fort Yuma.
    - Typescript B: Part II, Prelude and Ch. I, The Civil War. (Box 17, Folder 35)
      Union Savers; 1861; Ft. Sumter; Missouri; Cen. Lyon; Benton Barracks; Sedalia.
    - Typescript B: Pt. II, Ch. II, With the Army of the Southwest. (Box 17, Folder 36)
      Sedalia; Arkansas 1862.
    - Typescript B: Pt. II, Ch. III, Vicksburg. (Box 17, Folder 37)
      (Also marked as Ch. V). Chickasaw Bluffs; Arkansas Post; Young's Point; Jackson; Vicksburg.
    - Typescript B: General Biographical and Genealogical Material. (Box 17, Folder 38)
      Steele family.
    - Typescript C: Early Life of Gen. Steele. (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Typescript C: Mexican War. (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Typescript C: California and Frontier. (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Typescript C: Beginning of Civil War; Missouri and Arkansas, 1861 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Typescript C: Vicksburg. (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Typescript C: Arkansas #1. (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Typescript C: Arkansas #2. (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Typescript C: Arkansas #3. (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Typescript C: Pensacola Dispatches. (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Typescript C: Blakely. (Box 18, Folder 48)
      Louisiana, Pensacola, Spanish Fort, Mobile, Montgomery, death of Lincoln, Appomattox.
    - Typescript C: Department of the Columbia. (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Typescript C: Lone Mountain. (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Typescript C: Miscellaneous. (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Manuscript of Biography and Miscellaneous Notes. # 1-5. (Box 18, Folder 52-56)
    Not arranged.
  - Miscellaneous printed material
    - Road Maps - Current (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Sarta Clava County [Calif] Growth Statistics 1800s (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Magazines and Clippings - Current oversize, placed on top of box (Box 18, Folder 59)
Additional Descriptive Material
Index
Note: 3-15-[3-7] equals Box 3, folder 15, items 3 to 7
Adair, John (Sr.). 6-74-12.
Adair, John, Jr. 6-72-1 (m.), 5(m.); 6-74-12(m.)
Adams, Edward Payson (d. 1897). 4-45-33; 4-46-48; 4-47-19, 20, 33, 54; 4-49-31; 4-51-1; 4-52-18; 5-55-30.
Adams, Robert, Jr. 5-63-12b; 6-68-4, 11.
Adams Express Company, New Orleans. 3-37-6; 4-47-52, 53.
Adjutant General's Office, Washington, D. C. 2-29-20; 7 (vol.)- recipient. [SEE ALSO: Army, Headquarters of the - Adjutant General's Office; War Department - Adjutant General's Office.]
Alabama. 4-53-18, 19. [SEE ALSO: Cities (Mobile, etc.); District of West Florida and South Alabama.]
Alabama River - Landings. 6-71-10.
Alaska. 6-86-15. [SEE ALSO: District of Alaska.]
Allen, Henry W. 2-29-3 (printed).
Allen Robert. 6-85-10 (copy).
Ambros & Segura. 6-71-11, 12.
Ambulance Detachments, Reserve Corps, Military Division of West Mississippi. 7 (vol.)- recipient.
Andalousia, Alabama. 4-49-8.
Anderson, Mrs. _____. 1-10-36.
Anderson, Archer. 4-54-1 (copy).
Anderson, Thomas C. 1-8-19.
Andrews, Christopher Columbus (1829-1922). 2-17-6; 2-28-26; 2-29-15; 2-30-28; 2-31-5; 3-32-1, 24; 3-34-13; 3-35-28; 3-36-7 (m.); 3-38-1, 2, 19; 3-39-5, 17, 19, 24; 3-40-18, 39a (tel.); 4-45-31, 32, 35; 4-46-4, 7, 10, 27, 30, 31 (copy), 46 (copy), 47, [48-50 (copies)], 51, 53; 4-47-8 (copy), [17-20 (copies)], 29, 33 (copy), 34, 54 (copy); 4-48-1, 5, 31; 4-49-15, 23, 30, 31; 4-50-15; 4-52-7, 9; 4-53-33; 4-54-13; 5-55-14, 18, 27, 28; 5-57-1, 18, 19, 31, 33, 37; 5-58-15; 6-72-9, 10 (printed); 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Apreza, Manuel Reyes. 5-63-15.
Arkansas. 1-3-6, 7, 9, 10, 12, 13; 1-4-2, 3; 1-5-7, 8, 9, 12; 1-6-[1-4]; 1-7-5, [8-12], 14; 1-8-6, 7, 9, 10, 13, 15, 16, 17, 19; 1-9-2, 3, [5-8], [11-14], [16-19], [22-25], [27-29]; 1-10-3, 5, 8, 11, 14, 34, [40-45]; 1-11-3, 4, 12, 16, 18, 24, 36, 37, 42 (map); 1-12-4, 8, 9, 14, 16; 1-13-1; 2-14-13; 2-15-15, 19, 22; 2-16-3, 8; 2-17-3; 2-18-12, 20, 24; 2-20-7, 18; 2-21-4, 14; 2-24-4, 14; 2-25-12, 15; 2-27-1, 14, 27, 2-30-25, 30, 31; 3-33-15, 33; 4-51-23; 4-52-40; 5-60-11; 6-71-5. [SEE ALSO: Cities (Little Rock, etc.); Department of Arkansas].
Arkansas. Department of SEE Department of Arkansas.
Armies of the United States, Headquarters (various). 1-11-19; 2-24-18; 4-44-18; 4-52-34 (m.).
Armstrong, I. S. 3-42-57.
Army, Headquarters of the - Adjutant General's Office. 6-71-4; 6-79-12. [SEE ALSO: Adjutant General's Office, Washington, D. C.; War Department-Adjutant General's Office].
Army and Division of West Mississippi. 4-46-1, 8, 17; 4-47-1, 9, 10, 21, 35, 55, 56; 4-48-[23-25], 32, 33; 4-49-[1-4]; 4-50-[3-6], [16-18]; 4-51-[2-4], 56, 57, 76, 77; 4-52-10, 11, 19, 20, [28-31], 36; 4-53-[1-3], 9, 10, 23, 24, [34-36], [47-49]; 4-54-2, 17, 18, [24-27]; 5-57-13, 14, 20, 21, 27, 34, 38; 5-58-2, 3, 8, 9, 12, 13, 19; 5-59-5, 31; 6-71-13.
Army Corps SEE 18th Army Corps; 1st Brigade, 3rd Division, 7th Army Corps; First (1st) Division, 13th Army Corps; 2nd Division, 7th Army Corps; 2nd Division, 16th Army Corps; 2nd Division, 13th Army Corps; 7th Army Corps; 16th Army Corps; 3rd Brigade, 3rd Division, 7th Army Corps; 3rd Division, 7th Army Corps; 13th Army Corps.
Army of the Border. 2-31-16.
Army of the Rio Grande. 5-62-18, 25, 40, 44.
Army Navy Journal. 5-57-39.
Arnold, Isaac W. [Isaac Newton 1815-1884?]. 1-10-28.
Artillery. SEE 18th New York Independent Battery; 15th Massachusetts Battery; 1st Indiana Heavy Artillery-Battery H; 1st Light Battery Indiana Volunteers; 1st Michigan Light Artillery-Battery G; 1st Missouri Light Artillery; 4th Battery Light Artillery, Massachusetts Veteran Volunteers; 2nd Battery Massachusetts Light Artillery; 2nd Connecticut Light Battery; 17th Ohio Battery; 7th Massachusetts Battery Light Artillery; 21st New York Battery; 26th New York Battery.
Artillery, Chief of SEE Division of West Mississippi-Chief of Artillery.
Asboth, Alexander Sandor (1811-1868). 4-44-31; 4-45-20 (copy), 21, 30; 4-46-2, 32, 33; 4-47-22, 23, 27, 36; 4-48-26, 34; 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Associated Alumni of the Pacific Coast. 6-79-13 (printed).
Astor, William Backhouse (1792-1875). 6-70-2 (printed).
Atkinson, George S. 3-38-43; 3-40-1; 3-41-18.
Ayres, E. D. 2-29-34; 3-33-1.
Atkinson, William. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Babbitt, Edwin Burr (d. 1881). [1-1-8?]; 6-75-7; 6-77-6.
Babcock, Orville Elias (1835-1884). 6-74-4 (tel.).
Bache, Alexander Dallas (1806-1867). 1-4-13.
Bacon, A. B. (District Attorney of Cameron County, Texas). 1-1-11
Badger, A. S. 4-47-37, 38.
Bailie, A. D. 3-37-1; 4-43-1.
Baker, J. L. 3-37-32, 43.
Balch, George Thatcher (d. 1894). 1-12-3 (stamp?); 2-26-11 (stamp).
Baldwin, Thomas. 3-30-19.
Baldwin, William Henry (d. 1898). 3-40-12.
Ballard, D. P. 3-40-2, 19, 28; 3-41-31; 3-42-1, 32, 33.
Ballard, D. W. (Governor of Oregon). 6-73-3.
Balli, _____. 6-71-14 (m.).
Banks, Nathaniel Prentiss (1816-1894). 1-12-8; 2-30-18 (m.).
Barber, L. E. 2-26-26.
Barber, Robert. 4-47-50.
Barnes, James. 3-40-20, 35; 3-42-31, 47; 4-43-14.
Barney, George A. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Barrancas, Florida. SEE District of West Florida.
Bartlett, Eliza M. 3-33-8.
Bates, Edward. 1-10-22.
[Baturoni], G. 6-71-14.
Baxter, G. W. 4-53-4.
Beach, G. B. 4-48-13.
Beattie, Adam. 3-36-36; 3-42-10; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Beaudry, R. H. 4-47-24.
Beauregard, Peter Gustavus Toutant (1818-1893). 4-53-50 (copy).
Bellegrove Mansion. 3-36-18 (m.); 3-37-7 (m.).
Bellows, Henry Whitney (1814-1882). 1-9-7b (copy).
Bench, Dennis. 6-73-3.
Bencham, Spencer C. (d. 1876). 2-28-12.
Benton, Thomas Hart, Jr. 2-14-3; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Berry, I. R. 2-29-34.
Bertram, Henry. 4-53-11 (tel.); 25 (tel.), [37-39 (tels.)].
Bertrand, C. P. 1-10-29; 2-15-9.
Bexter, E. 1-9-17a.
Bidwell, John (1819-1900). 6-72-1 (copy).
Big Creek, Arkansas-Skirmish. 2-22-1.
Binney, Mrs. Amos. 1-10-47.
Bishop, Daniel E. 3-35-7 (m.).
Black, James R. 7 (vol.)-recipient; [8 (Vol.)-recipient].
Black, [John] Charles (1839-1915). 3-35-14; 3-37-21, 23, 24; 3-38-23, 41; 3-39-1; 3-40-3; 3-41-1, 40, 41; 4-43-15, 29; 4-44-4; 5-57-40; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Black, William W. 3-40-9.
Blair, Francis (Frank) Preston, Jr. (1821-1875). 1-6-6.
Blakely, Alabama. 4-48-21; 4-51-6, 44, 83, 86, 90; 4-52-1, 2, 19, 20; 4-53-17; 4-54-25; 5-55-33; 7 (vol.)-(m.); 8 (vol.)-(m.).
Blakely, Alabama-Maps. 5-56-[1-5]. [SEE ALSO: Mobile, Alabama; Pensacola, Florida; Spanish Fort, Alabama].
Blakley, T. M. 3-34-36
Bliss, C. C. (Lt. Governor of Arkansas). 2-15-35; 3-33-1; 3-35-22; 5-65-2 (m.).
Board of Examiners of Commissaries of Subsistence-6th District, New Orleans. 5-55-8.
Boca Chica Pass, Texas. 5-62-21, 22 (map); 7 (vol.)-(m.).
Boise, Idaho. SEE District of Boise; Fort Boise, Idaho.
Bolton, Mississippi-Map. 6-88-1.
Bowers, Theodore S. (d. 1866). 1-7-13; 1-8-2; 4-44-18.
Bowsman, Thomas J. 5-64-25.
Boyd, S. H. 1-9-21.
Boyle, William. 4-46-25; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Bozman, R. M. 5-66-3, 4, 21.
Breck, [Samuel]. 1-9-4.
[Bredinburgh], John S. 3-32-1.
Brenham, C. J. 6-72-5.
Brewster & Co., New York. 6-71-[1-3].
Brooke, Lloyd. 6-75-10.
Brooks, Ben H. 6-72-2a, 3; [6-88-2?].
Brown, Alfred. 2-28-16a.
Brown, Egbert Benson (1816-1902). 5-61-26, 30 (m.); 5-62-7; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Brown, Joseph H. 2-28-27.
Brown, M. C. 3-35-12.
Brownsville, Texas. 5-61-22; 5-63-10; 5-64-15; 6-69-1; 7 (vol.).-(m.).
Brownsville, Texas-Junta Patriotica Mejicana. 6-69-7.
Bruce, Mrs. M. E. 2-26-20.
Buchanan, [M.?]. 3-32-10.
Buckland, Ralph Pomeroy (1812-1892). 1-10-14.
Buell, Don Carlos (1818-1898). 1-1-6/
Buford, Napoleon Bonaparte (1807-1883). 1-11-5 (m.).
Bullock, W. F. Jr. 5-55-9.
Burbridge, Stephen Gano (1831-1894). 2-20-10.
Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen, and Abandoned Lands. 5-58-25 (m.); 5-59-3. [SEE ALSO: War Department-Bureau of Refugees, Freedmen, and Abandoned Lands].
Burke, F. N. 2-31-10 (printed.).
Burnham, Arthur Hubert (d. 1877). 4-50-19.
Burr, E. T. 2-26-14.
Busey, Samuel Thompson (1835-1909). 4-45-31, 32; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Bushwiler, Aaron. 6-86-3, 4 (copy), 5, 6 (copy).
Butler, James A. 3-32-23; 3-35-22.
Cabella, J. Maria. 5-59-27.
Caldwell, W. S. 6-84-1, 2(Copy), 5, 6 (copy).
Caldwell Expedition. 3-32-18.
California SEE Department of California.
Camden, Arkansas. 1-11-36, 37; 2-19-18.
Camden, Arkansas-Campaign. 1-12-9, 16; 1-13-11, 12, 20.
Cameron, Simon. 1-1-16 (photocopy).
Cameron County, Texas. 1-1-11.
Camp C. F. Smith, Oregon. 6-80-6.
Camp Steele, San Juan Island, Washington. 6-83-3.
Camp Warner, Oregon. 6-79-11.
Campbell, B. H. 2-17-7; 2-30-4.
Canby, Edward Richard Sprigg (1817-1873). 2-29-11 (tel.), 17, 21 (tel.); 2-30-7 (copy); 3-32-7 (copy), 11 (copy); 4-49-16; 4-50-20 (tel.), 21 (tel.); 4-51-58 (tel.), 59 (tel.), 78 (tel.); 5-55-31 (tel.); 5-57-24 (tel.); 5-59-32 (tel.); 5-60-1; 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Carper, [Leo?]. 2-18-2, 13; 2-21-11.
Carr, Byron Oscar. 1-11-39; 1-12-12; 2-17-2; 2-23-15; 2-30-2, 14.
Case, Loyal. 1-11-28; 3-34-19.
Cavalry. SEE 1st Louisiana Cavalry; 1st Regiment Florida Cavalry; 2nd Battalion Nebraska Cavalry; 2nd Illinois Cavalry; 2nd Regiment Main Veteran Volunteer Cavalry; 2nd Veteran New York Cavalry Volunteers; Separate Cavalry Brigade-Barrancas, Florida; 3rd Iowa Cavalry; 3rd Michigan Cavalry; 13th Illinois Cavalry Volunteers.
Cavalry, Chief of SEE Division of West Mississippi-Chief of Cavalry.
Chalfin, Samuel Fletcher (d. 1891). 2-29-20.
Chancellorsville, Virginia, Battles of. 1-4-7 (map); 2-26-28. [SEE ALSO: Suffolk-Chancellorsville].
Chandler, J. L. 1-12-5, 6, 7, 23, 24, 25; 2-30-25, 30, 31.
Chandler, W. 2-21-34.
Chapman, Edmund Drake (d. 1894). 2-25-17 (copy).
Cheney, A. O. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Christensen, Christian Thomsen. 1-9-1; 2-15-17; 2-28-[17-19], 20; 2-29-17; 2-30-22; 3-34-32 (copy); 3-36-9, [12-16], 19, [27-29], 35, 37, 38; 3-37-2, 3, 13, 21, 25, 33, 38, 39, 44, 45; 3-38-[4-6], 13, [25-27], 31, [36-38]; 3-39-2, 8, 9, [12-14], 16, [20-22], [28-30], [32-34], 37, 38; 3-40-13; 3-41-11, 12, 19, 20, [32-35]; 3-42-12; 4-43-2, 3, 16, 17; 4-44-10; 4-45-13, 28; 4-46-9, 34; 4-47-11, 14; 4-50-[9-11], 13, 22 (tel.); 4-51-5, [13-19 (tels.)], [31-36 (tels.)], 37, [60-61 (tels.)], [79-81 (tels.)], 91; 4-52-[1-3], [11-13], 15, 21, 26, 32, 36, 39; 4-53-7, 12, 13, 14 (tel.), 18, [40-44 (tels.)], 51 (tel.); 4-54-3; 5-60-10; 6-71-8, 13, 15 (tel.); 7 (vol.)-recipient; 8 (vol.)-recipient.
Chroniger, C. B. 5-65-13; 5-66-18; 5-67-[18-20]; 6-68-9.
Chrysler, Morgan Henry (1822-1890). 4-47-49; 5-57-28; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Clark, Charles E. - Court Martial of. 2-27-22 (m.).
Clark, George Washington (d. 1898). 3-39-5; 3-40-39b; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Clark, William Thomas (183101905). 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Clarke, P. J. (Catholic priest, Pine Bluff, Arkansas). 2-31-6.
Clarke, William Hyde. 2-28-[17-19]
Claveron, D. W. [Toribio?]. 6-71-14 (m.).
Clayton, Powell (1833-1914). 2-21-1 (m.); 3-32-20; 3-34-32.
Clinton, DeWitt (d 1873). 2-19-1; [2-30-26?].
Coates, James Henry. 3-38-42; 4-44-5; 6-71-16.
Cockrell, Francis Marion (1834-1915). 4-51-88 (copy).
Coleman, W. P. 3-36-18; 3-37-7.
Coles, Charles. 6-88-13a (printed).
Colored Regiments, etc. SEE Corps d'Afrique; 82nd U. S. Colored Infantry; 86th Regiment U. S. Colored Infantry; 11th U. S. Colored Brigade; 50th U. S. Cologed Infantry; 1st Division U. S. Colored Troops; 47th Regiment U. S. Colored Infantry; 76th U. S. Colored Infantry; 25th Regiment U. S. Colored Infantry.
Columbia SEE Department of the Columbia.
Commissaries of Subsistence. SEE Board of Examiners of Commissaries of Subsistence.
Conduct of the War, U. S. Senate Committee on the 5-59-18a.
Connecticut Regiments, etc. SEE 2nd Connecticut Light Battery.
Cooke, Phillip St. George (1809-1895). 2-22-11.
Coolidge, Mary Eva. 2-31-10 (printed).
Corbett, Henry Winslow (1827-1903). 6-80-3.
Corps d'Afrique. 2-19-15; 2-20-23; 2-21-22.
Cortina, Juan Nepomuceno. 5-61-26 (m.); 5-62-19 (m.), 38 (m.); 5-63-4 (m.), 9 (m.), 10 (m.), 16, 17, 21 (m.), 22 (m.); 5-64-1, 2, 10 (m.), 11 (m.); 5-67-11, 12; 6-68-1, 16 (m.); 6-71-23 (m.); 7 (vol.)-(m.), recipient.
Cotton Creek, Florida. 4-49-7.
Crandell, Theo [R. or K.?]. 3-39-5; 3-40-39b.
Crawford, James. 6-84-1, 2 (copy).
Crebs, John Montgomery (1830-1890). 2-30-21.
Crittenden, Thomas Theodore (1832-1909). 1-8-14.
Crook, George (1828-1890). 6-80-6; 6-82-5 (m.); 6-84-15 (m.).
Crosby, J. Schuyler. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Crowell, Nathaniel Savage. 1-1-7.
Crowl, E. W. 2-26-26.
Crowl, W. C. 3-32-23.
Cullum, George Washington (1809-1892). 1-1-5 (printed); 1-2-5; 3-36-2.
Cunningham, C. H. 5-60-2.
Curtis, Elijah P. 3-40-37.
Curtis, Henry Z. (d. 1863). 1-3-12 (copy).
Curtis, Robert Galpin. 4-49-18.
Curtis, Samuel Ryan (1805-1866). 1-3-7.
Custer, George Armstrong (1839-1876). 5-62-42 (m.); 6-75-2 (m.).
Danovan, Thomas. 2-31-17.
Davidson, Delozier. 4-44-21 (m.).
Davidson, John Wynn (1824-1881). 1-7-15; 1-9-20 (m.), 21 (m.); 1-10-1; 1-12-[5-7], [23-25] (m.)] 2-15-36 (m.); 2-21-16 (m.); 2-29-1; 6-88-2 (m.), 6 (m.).
Davis, Jefferson (1808-1889). 5-57-1 (m.).
Davis, Levi. 3-37-8, 34.
Day, John [H.]. 4-52-37.
Defences of New Orleans. 3-40-21, 29; 3-42-2; 3-42-2, 22, 34, 48; 4-43-18.
Dethart, E. I. 6-75-10.
Deitzler, George Washington. (1826-1884) 2-15-29.
De Leon, F. SEE Leon, Francisco de
Denicke, C. M. 5-55-32.
Denison, J. M. 3-35-12.
Dennis, Elias Smith (1812-1894). 3-36-24; 3-37-[9-12]; 3-38-34, 42; 3-40-30; 4-44-20b; 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Department of Arkansas. 1-9-23; 1-10-3, 6, 12, 24, 25, 27, 32; 1-11-3, 8, 9, 15, 17, 30, 31; 1-12-1, 13, 15, 19, 21; 1-13-9, 10; 2-14-1, [10-12]; 2-15-1, 4, 8, 10, 11, 13, 16, 20, 21, 27; 2-16-1, 4, 9, 13; 2-17-4, 10, 11, 14; 2-18-1, 5, 15, 22; 2-19-9, 11, 17; 2-20-6, 11, 12, 15, [28-31]; 2-21-7, 18, 27; 2-22-7; 2-23-1, 9, 2-23-20, 22, 23; 2-24-1, 9, 17; 2-26-4, 23, 24; 2-28-4, [17-19 (m.)]; 2-29-18; 2-30-12, 15; 2-31-1, 9, 11, 18, 23; 3-32-2, 3, 12, 14; 3033-31; 3-34-1, 9, 14, 24; 3-35-21; 3-36-1.
Department of Arkansas-Office, Provost Marshall General. 1-10-15.
Department of California. 6-75-4.
Department of Louisiana. 5-64-7. [SEE ALSO: Louisiana].
Department of Mississippi. 3-42-3.
Department of Texas SEE 1st Provisional District, Department of Texas.
Department of the Columbia. 6-68-5 (m.); 6-72-7, 8; 6-73-5, 6 (m.), 11; 6-74-1, 5, 10, 14; 6-75-[7-9]; 6-76-1, 3, 4, 8, 9; 6-77-1, 2; 6-78-3, [6-13]; 6-79-1, 2, 5, [7-10], 14, 15; 6-80-1, 4, 9, 10; 6-81-1, 6; 6-82-1, 4, 6, 10; 6-83-[1-3], 7; 6-85-1, 5, 7, 9; 6-86-1, 2, 7, 9, 10 (m.), 11a, 12, 13.
Department of the Gulf. 1-10-46 (map); 2-19-15 (m.); 3-37-35, 36; 3-38-3; 5-61-28.
Department of the Gulf-Office, Chief Signal Officer. 4-45-33.
Department of the West-St. Louis, Missouri. 1-1-6.
DeValls Bluff, Arkansas. 1-5-9; 1-11-10 (map); 2-28-26; 2-29-15; 2-30-28; 2-31-24, 25; 3-34-13.
Dexter, John Bangs (d.1883). 4-46-24.
Dicken, J. L. 1-3-12 (copy); 3-41-3.
District of Alaska. 6-86-10. [SEE ALSO: Alaska].
District of Boise. 6-77-4. [SEE ALSO; Fort Boise, Idaho].
District of Eastern Arkansas. 2-21-34.
District of Texas. 5-61-29; 5-62-[3-5], 14, 37.
District of West Florida (Barrancas). 3-39-26, 27, 36; 3-41-21; 3-42-4, 23, 49; 4-43-35, 37, 41; 4-44-1, 9, 16, 31, 32; 4-46-35, 36; 4-47-23; 4-48-2, 35, 36.
District of West Florida and South Alabama (Ft. Gaines). 4-44-19, 22, [27-29]; 4-45-8; 4-46-19, 20; 4-47-25, 26. [SEE ALSO: Alabama].
Divicione Mejia-Parque de Artilleria. 5-59-27.
Division Mejia, La. 5-65-11.
Division of Mississippi-Raleigh, North Carolina. 5-55-10.
Division of the Gulf. 5-62-41; 5-63-12b; 6-68-4, 11.
Division of the Mississippi, Military. 1-7-2, 4, 13; 1-8-2, 3, 7, 11; 1-10-4, 7, 10, 17, 33, 37; 1-11-22, 23, 35, 38; 1-12-2, 10-11, 18, 22; 2-18-2, 13; 2-21-11; 2-23-11; 2-24-7, 12, 19; 2-30-20, 21.
Division of West Mississippi, Military. 2-15-5, 14, 17, [23-25], 28, 31, 32, 35; 2-16-7, 10, 14; 2-17-1; 2-18-3, 4, [6-8], [16-18], 23; 2-19-2, 7, 12, 15; 2-20-1, 9, 13, 16, 19, 23, 32; 2-21-2, 3, 8, 9, 12, 19, 20, 22, 28, 32; 2-22-4, 8; 2-23-4, 8, 10, 17, 18, 26; 2-24-2, 6, 13, 20, 24, 25; 2-25-6, 9, 18; 2-26-5, 12, 13, 15, 27; 2-27-17, 21, 22; 2-28-5, 6, 21, 22; 2-29-[2-6], 9, 12, 16, 28; 2-30-23; 2-31-2, 3, 7; 3-32-15, 21, 25; 3-33-3, 14, 18, 20, 25, 26; 3-34-2, 15, 16, [20-22], [25-28], 30, 31, [33-35], 38, 39; 3-35-1, 7, 18; 3-36-3, 4, 11, 12, 15, 16, 19, [25-29], 37, 38; 3-37-2, 3, 13, 25, [37-39], 44, 45; 3-38-[4-6], 14, [24-27], [35-38]; 3-39-2, [6-9], 21, 22, 28, 29, [31-34], 37, 38; 3-40-4, [14-17], 22, 31, 32; 3-41-4, 13, [22-24], [36-39]; 3-42-[5-7], [13-15], 24, 25, [35-39], [50-52]; 4-43-[4-7], 19, [23-26], 34, [42-44]; 4-44-2, [10-12], 20a, [23-25], 33, 34; 4-45-[1-3], 16, 17, 22, 23, 28; 5-58-27; 5-59-6 (m.), 21, 28, 39; 7 (vol.)-(m.).
Division of West Mississippi, Military-Office Chief of Cavalry. 2-18-14; 2-19-10; 2-20-5, 14; 2-27-12.
Division of West Mississippi, Military-Office of Assistant Inspector General. 2-20-4; 2-21-29; 2-26-16; 3-36-5, 39.
Division of West Mississippi, Military-Office of the Chief of Artillery. 2-31-4.
Division of West Mississippi, Military-Office of the Chief of Artillery and Ordnance. 3-32-22; 3-33-32; 3-36-17; 3-40-5.
Dolan, M. 7 (vol.)-recipient.
Doty, W. D. 4-47-49.
Drake, Francis Marion. 1-12-17.
Drew, Charles Wilson (d. 1903). 4-46-6, 37; 4-47-47.
D[rune?], R. C. 6-72-6.
Dug Springs, Missouri-Battle. 1-1-14.